yousaytoo.com 2007-12-03

# YouSayToo.com - Revenue sharing community

**1\. FIRST NAME, LAST NAME**

This information is obligatory for the registration of an account at www.yousaytoo.com. This information is accessible to the registered users only. A user may choose to show that information to other registered users. You confirm that you provide truthful information during the registration; if you provide unreliable information, you may violate the rights of third persons; in that case, you may bear responsibility under the legislation of the Republic of Latvia. www.yousaytoo.com does not share users' personal information with advertisers and does not use it in its other projects; it does not transfer that information to third persons. www.yousaytoo.com does not use that information for commercial purposes either. Users' personal information is protected by the legislation of the Republic of Latvia. 

**2\. AGE**

This information is obligatory for the registration of an account at www.yousaytoo.com. The resource may be used by adult users only; minors have no right to have an account at www.yousaytoo.com (due to adult content). If an account is discovered, which has been registered by a minor, that account will be closed immediately. A user may choose to show that information to other registered users. www.yousaytoo.com does not share users' personal information with advertisers and does not use it in its other projects; it does not transfer that information to third persons. www.yousaytoo.com does not use that information for commercial purposes either. Users' personal information is protected by the legislation of the Republic of Latvia. 

**3\. SEX**

This information is not obligatory for the registration. www.yousaytoo.com does not share users personal information with advertisers and does not use it in its other projects; it does not transfer that information to third persons. www.yousaytoo.com does not use that information for commercial purposes either. Users' personal information is protected by the legislation of the Republic of Latvia. 

**4\. CITY, COUNTRY**

This information is not obligatory for the registration of an account at www.yousaytoo.com. You confirm that you provide truthful information during the registration; if you provide unreliable information, you may violate the rights of third persons; in that case, you may bear responsibility under the legislation of the Republic of Latvia. www.yousaytoo.com does not share users' personal information with advertisers and does not use it in its other projects; it does not transfer that information to third persons. www.yousaytoo.com does not use that information for commercial purposes either. Users' personal information is protected by the legislation of the Republic of Latvia. 

**5\. ADVERTISING**

www.yousaytoo.com is not responsible for advertisements at the resource. All the ads at www.yousaytoo.com are provided by Google AdSense. www.yousaytoo.com does not perform any financial operations with www.yousaytoo.com users. www.yousaytoo.com does not share users' personal information with advertisers. www.yousaytoo.com is not responsible for the advertisers' Cookies. 

**6\. E-MAIL**

Obligatory information necessary during registration for the confirmation of registration. This information is treated as confidential. www.yousaytoo.com does not share that information with advertisers and does not use it in its other projects; it does not transfer that information to third persons. www.yousaytoo.com does not use that information for commercial purposes either. Users' personal information is protected by the legislation of the Republic of Latvia. 

**7\. WEBSITE**

This information is not obligatory for the registration. www.yousaytoo.com does not share users personal information with advertisers and does not use it in its other projects; it does not transfer that information to third persons. www.yousaytoo.com does not use that information for commercial purposes either. Users' personal information is protected by the legislation of the Republic of Latvia. 

**8\. AdSense ID, AdSense ID Channel**

This information is not obligatory for the registration. This information is treated as confidential. www.yousaytoo.com does not share that information with advertisers and does not use it in its other projects; it does not transfer that information to third persons. www.yousaytoo.com does not use that information for commercial purposes either. Users' personal information is protected by the legislation of the Republic of Latvia. 

**9\. BIO**

This information is not obligatory for the registration. www.yousaytoo.com does not share users' personal information with advertisers and does not use it in its other projects; it does not transfer that information to third persons. www.yousaytoo.com does not use that information for commercial purposes either. Users' personal information is protected by the legislation of the Republic of Latvia. 

**10\. USERNAME**

This information is obligatory for the registration and subsequent use of the www.yousaytoo.com resource, it is accessible to all registered and unregistered www.yousaytoo.com users. Maximum 12 symbols may be used for the username; punctuation marks and four-letter words cannot be used. The users have no right to change the username. If an account was closed, the username is not restored. www.yousaytoo.com does not share users' that information with advertisers and does not use it in its other projects; it does not transfer that information to third persons. www.yousaytoo.com does not use that information for commercial purposes either. 

**11\. IP ADDRESS**

www.yousaytoo.com controls IP addresses in order to analyze and prevent technical problems associated with IP addresses, to know where and how many users www.yousaytoo.com has, to follow and prevent threats, violence and persecution. 

Till five accounts are envisaged for one IP address; and user has no right to evaluate accounts located at one IP address. www.yousaytoo.com does not share the users' personal information with advertisers, and does not use it in its other projects; it does not transfer that information to third persons. www.yousaytoo.com does not use that information for commercial purposes either. 

**12\. E-MAIL CHOICE**

The user has the right to change e-mail, in order to do that, user must use feedback form and provide a valid reason for changing the e-mail, as well as the new e-mail address. 

**13\. RATING**

www.yousaytoo.com does not share the users personal information with other users, advertisers, and does not use it in its other projects; it does not transfer that information to third persons. www.yousaytoo.com does not use that information for commercial purposes either. Users' personal information is protected by the legislation of the Republic of Latvia. 

**14\. CHANGES TO Privacy Policy**

www.yousaytoo.com has the right to correct, change, add Privacy Policy at www.yousaytoo.com discretion without informing the users about it. 

**15\. CONTACT WEBSERVICE**

If you have propositions and questions regarding PrivacyPolicy, please write to this address, and we would be happy to reply.
